Guide to the John Ewart Wallace Sterling, Chancellor of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Series 2
  - Aitken, Sir Robert, 1963-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Barclay, Thomas S., Prof. Emeritus, 1957-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bastedo, G. M., 1952-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bastedo & Victoria University (also see Bastedo, G. M.), 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Confidential, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Crank Correspondence, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sir Samuel Curran, 1970-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Disputers, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - International Migration of Talent From and to the Less-Developed Countries, 1968 Feb. 16-19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Foundations and Government, 1966 Nov. 18-21 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Anatomy of Anglo-American Relations, 1962 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The International Monetary System: An American Perspective, 1966 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Evolving Commonwealth, 1970 Sept. 25 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Collective Bargaining in Transition, 1969 Nov. 14-17 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Trade Policies in the Atlantic Area, 1969 Dec. 5-8 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Responsibilities of Communications Media, 1970 Jan. 9-12 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Student and Universities, 1969 Feb. 7-10 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ditchley Foundation Newsletter, 1970 Sept.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ditchley Foundation Newsletter, 1970 Jan.-April (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ditchley Foundation Newsletter, 1969 May-July (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Ditchley Foundation Newsletter, 1969 Jan.-April (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ditchley Foundation Newsletter, 1968 Sept.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Council's Annual Report and Accounts, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Council's Annual Report and Accounts, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - The Council's Annual Report and Accounts, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Council's Annual Report and Accounts, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The Ditchley Foundations Booklet, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Ditchley Foundations Booklet, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Ditchley The Anglo-American Conference Centre, 1964 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ditchley The Anglo-American Conference Centre: Ditchley Park, March 21 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Council's Annual Report and Accounts, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Conference on Taxation and Economic Growth, 1968 April 26-29 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Newsletter to Governors of Ditchley and Members of the Advisory Council of the American Ditchley Foundation, 1968 Jan. 16 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Ditchley Foundation: A Newsletter from the Provost, 1971 Jan.-April (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Ditchley Foundation: A Newsletter from the Provost, 1971 May-July (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Council's Annual Report and Accounts, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ditchley Foundation: A Newsletter from the Provost, 1968 May-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Ditchley Foundation The American Committee, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - The Ditchley Foundation The American Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - The Ditchley Foundation, 1957-1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - The Ditchley Foundation, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Ditchley Foundation, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - The Ditchley Foundation, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - The Ditchley Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Employment Inquiries, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - John W. Gardner, 1973-1984 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Gift Acknowledgements Miscellaneous, 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Gloucester (Duchess of:), 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Prince William, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Photo of Duchess of Gloucester, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Prince William, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Ditchley Foundation: Conference on Moral Values in Education, 1967 March 31-April 3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Honors, 1952-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Wallace Award-1980 - American-Scottish Foundation, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Commander of the British Empire", 1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - KBE - Honorary Knighthood, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Gordon Kerr, 1968-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - William R. Kimball, 1974-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Lane/Sunset, 1962-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)